A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller personal papers, Projects, Series L FA348
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Graham, Horace R., 1943-1951 (Box 75, Folder 720)
  Mutual business friends. Coordination Committee for Chile. Illness due to accident. Imporvement.
- Grand Street Boys Association, 1945-1965 (Box 75, Folder 721)
  NAR becomes LIfe Member in 1945. Special contributions. Sends autographed photograph.
- Grand Street Boys Association - Grand Street Boys Association Foundation, 1952-1960 (Box 75, Folder 722)
  Anonymous NAR contribution in 1954.
- Gray, J. Spencer - "The Herald of Westchester", 1957-1961 (Box 75, Folder 723)
  Editor and publisher of "The Herald of Westchester." Offered to support NAR for Governor. Sought financial aid through advertising.
- Great Books of the Western World, 1949-1961 (Box 75, Folder 724)
  Clippings, photo of dinner, formal presentation dinner folder. NAR a charter subscriber, helped with subscriptions. Correspondents include Robert M. Hutchins, William Benton, Mortimer J. Adler.
- Great Island Conference, 1946 (Box 75, Folder 725)
  Pamphlets and more literature. NAR resigns from Conference. Notes of meetings. Correspondents include Beardsley Ruml, Martha Dalrymple, Eric Hodgkins.
- Great Island Conference, 1947 (Box 76, Folder 726)
- Greater New York Fund, 1949-1965 (Box 76, Folder 727)
  John Davison Rockefeller 3rd Chairman in 1949. NAR contributions. Solicitation of Office Staff. Contributions by office and family.
- Greenwich House, 1934-1951 (Box 76, Folder 728)
  NAR declined contribution since his parents give $500 per year. Correspondents include Mary Simkhovitch.
- Gregory, Ernest T., 1951-1957 (Box 76, Folder 729)
  Resume. Meets with NAR. Denied position in Brazil due to language problem. Interview with E.K. Langstaff.
- Grew, Joseph C. Honorable, 1945 (Box 76, Folder 730)
  Sends the "Argonaut." Save the Redwoods League. NAR thanks for his work in the surrender of Japan. Response.
- Gruenther, Gen. Alfred M., 1955-1956 (Box 76, Folder 731)
  Party in London, American Red Cross, North Atlantic Treaty Organization. NAR sends flowers on operation.
- Gubbins, Reynaldo, 1953-1958 (Box 76, Folder 732)
  Clipping from "The Washington Post." Appeal to the United Nations to end landlock of Bolivia. "History of Our Claims Against the U.S.A." Blacklisting of Sounth American companies and individuals.
- Guin, Dr. Connie M., 1955-1963 (Box 76, Folder 733)
  Laurance Spelman Rockefeller spoke at dedication of Dr. Guin Building of New York Hospital. Copy of Laurance Spelman Rockefeller correspondence. Check of gratitude from the brothers. Sends the story of Sweet Briar College. Invites NAR to dedication of building.
- Gulick, Luther, 1948-1955 (Box 76, Folder 734)
  Sends "Administrative Reflections from World War II." Better comics for adolescents. Study of the New York City Department of Commerce. Correspondents include Otto Nelson, Francis Jamieson.
- Guzman, Melcher, 1947-1968 (Box 76, Folder 735)
  Tenant of Rockefeller Center. Approached NAR with business proposals. All declined.
- Ha-Hals, 1942-1971 (Box 77, Folder 736)
  Appeals for aid; job applicants; suggested projects; requests for information.
- Ham-Haz, 1942-1971 (Box 77, Folder 737)
- He, 1942-1971 (Box 77, Folder 738)
- Hi, 1942-1971 (Box 77, Folder 739)
- Ho-Hol, 1942-1971 (Box 77, Folder 740)
- Hom-Hoy, 1942-1971 (Box 77, Folder 741)
- Hr-Hy, 1942-1971 (Box 77, Folder 742)
- Haden, Allen, no date (Box 78, Folder 743)
  Proposed Sunday supplement, international magazine. "In Defense of Nelson Rockefeller."
- Hall, E. K., Jr., 1957-1958 (Box 78, Folder 744)
  "American Policy and Propaganda with Regard to the Union of Soviet Socialist Republics and the Satellite Countries." "Tough Business - Communist." Would like funds to start newsletters to analyze Soviet Affairs. Declined. Correspondents include Victor Borella.
- Hallauer, Carl S., 1947-1952 (Box 78, Folder 745)
  NAR sends letters of introduction for him on South American trip. Would also like name of person at United Nations for tour.
- Halle, Louis J. Jr., 1948-1955 (Box 78, Folder 746)
  Sends articles; "Cooperative Agricultural Programs of the Institute for Inter-American Affairs," "Civilization and Foreign Policy."
- Halpert, Edith Mrs., 1932-1954 (Box 78, Folder 747)
  Orders Alabaster Car, other art works. Thanks Rockefellers for their support of the Downtown Gallery. Correspondents include Alfred Barr.
- Hammond, Lawrence, 1946-1951 (Box 78, Folder 748)
  "Keeping Up With the Wigglesorths" - scenes from radio. Would like Francis A. Jamieson's opinion. Sir William Gibson-Craig-Carmichael. Would like to talk about a radio program. Correspondents include Francis A. Jamieson.
- Handicapped, Institutions & Organizations, 1959-1970 (Box 78, Folder 749)
  Appeals declined. Previous to 1959 discarded.
- Handicapped, Institutions & Organizations - Blind, Miscellaneous (A-Z) and Institutions, 1958-1971 (Box 78, Folder 750)
  Appeals declined. Previous to 1958 destroyed.
- Handicapped, Institutions & Organizations - Blind - American Foundation for the Blind, American Foundation for the Overseas Blind, 1953-1969 (Box 78, Folder 751)
  Form appeals declined.
- Handicapped, Institutions & Organizations - Blind - The Lighthouse, New York Association for the Blind, 1938-1971 (Box 78, Folder 752)
  NAR contributions.
- Handicapped, Institutions & Organizations - Blind - The Seeing Eye, 1935-1937 (Box 78, Folder 753)
  Appeals for contributions. Arthur W. Packard's 1935 analysis of Program. NAR contributions. Membership in "Seeing Eye" Organization. Book: "Dogs as Guides for the Blind." Correspondents include NAR, Arthur W. Packard, Miss H. Eustis.
- Handicapped, Institutions & Organizations - Deaf & Speech Problems, Miscellaneous (A-Z), 1970-1971 (Box 78, Folder 754)
- Handicraft Development, Inc. - House of Italian Handicrafts, 1945-1952 (Box 78, Folder 755)
  NAR sponsorship. Report on projected operations. Opening. NAR contribution. Max Ascoli sends album. Correspondents include Max Ascoli, Bruno Foa.
- Hanks, Nancy, 1957-1970 (Box 78, Folder 756)
  Clippings, correspondence re projects and activities. Nancy Hanks' appointment as Chairman of National Council for the Arts.
- Hannah, John A. Dr., 1951-1957 (Box 79, Folder 757)
  President of Michigan State College. Venezuelan situation. Economic Development Conference. Sends gifts. Assistant Secretary of Defense. Invites NAR to 100th Anniversary. Chairman of Civil Rights Commission.
- Hanson, Simon - Hanson Associates, 1946-1952 (Box 79, Folder 758)
  Report on Brazilian situation. Suggests an official commission to inquire into United States-Latin American policy. Hanson's Latin American letter. "Economic Sense in Latin America." Correspondents include John White.
- Hanson, Wayne, 1947-1950 (Box 79, Folder 759)
  Resume and brochure. Would like a contact in Caracas. Introduced to Bernardo Jofre. Will visit New York City April 21.
- Hardesty, Mortimer N., 1954-1955 (Box 79, Folder 760)
  Booklet returned. Sends copy of presentation before the House Foreign AFfairs Committee. Congratulates NAR on appointment with the (United States Department of) Health, Education and Welfare.
- Harman, William H. Corporation, 1948 (Box 79, Folder 761)
  Laurance Spelman Rockefeller sends report of the corporation. Harman homes. Correspondents include Laurance Spelman Rockefeller.
- Harding, William Barclay, 1946-1956 (Box 79, Folder 762)
  "Progress Report on Certain Major Revenue Bond Projects." Personal notes. Views on Washington appointments. Thanks NAR for flowers. Correspondents include Laurance Spelman Rockefeller, Robert Cutler.
- Harless, Richard Fielding, 1948 (Box 79, Folder 763)
  United States Representative from Arizona. Meets with NAR re International Basic Economy Corporation. Correspondents include Kenneth Kadow.
- Harriman, W. Averell, 1951-1961 (Box 79, Folder 764)
  Hope to see one another. Glad for John Davison Rockefeller, Jr.'s gift to United Nations. NAR glad Harriman will be Chief European Representative of ECA. NAR recommends Rene Bonche as artist.
- Harrison, John L. & Mrs., 1965 (Box 79, Folder 765)
  Correspondence re summer rental of house for summer of 1965.
- Haskell, Harry G. Jr., 1943-1965 (Box 79, Folder 766)
  Correspondence to, from and about Mr. Haskell, his activities, his 1956 election to Congress, his defeat in 1958, and personal concerns.
- Health - General Correspondence, 1953-1971 (Box 79, Folder 767)
  Material and correspondence on the World Health Organization; appeals from health organizations declined.
- Health - Health and Sanitation Service Agreements, 1946 (Box 79, Folder 768)
  Possibility of American International Association for Social and Economic Development (AIA) taking over Institute of Inter-American Affairs' Health and Sanitation Agreements with Latin American governments. Correspondents include George C. Dunham, Harold B. Gotaas.
- Hedrick, Paul H., 1953-1966 (Box 79, Folder 769)
  Correspondence re proposals for projects in Latin America.
- Heffelfinger, Mrs. F. Peavey, 1957-1960 (Box 79, Folder 770)
  Correspondence re meetings with NAR and her interests in Asia Society and Republican Party.
- Heilperin, Michael A., 1952-1953 (Box 79, Folder 771)
  "Economic Nationalism as an Obstacle to Free World Unity." Economic report for Bristol Myers. Report on trip to Paris (Indo-China issue). Correspondents include Charles Wheeler.
- Heinz, Henry John II, 1949-1956 (Box 79, Folder 772)
  Notes on visit to England, July 1949. MacLeish and Mumford proposal. "Investment for Policy and Profit." NAR recommended to Sherman Adams. Correspondents include Sigurd Larmon.
- Hemispheric Stock Exchange Conference, 1950 (Box 79, Folder 773)
  Information Bulletin. Excerpts from Minutes and Meetings. Clippings. NAR addresses Conference. F. A. Truslow address at dinner. Correspondents include Rafael Oreamuno, J.D. d'Oliveira.
- Henius, Frank, 1946-1953 (Box 79, Folder 774)
  Mutual news, his dictionary of foreign trade. Wants to discuss idea with NAR. Post cards. Publicity re his language books, Spanish record album, 16th Century painting, Mr. Pifferi.
- Henry Street Settlement, Visiting Nurse Service, 1935-1941 (Box 79, Folder 775)
  Appeals for aid. Small NAR contributions, later increased. Correspondents include John Schiff, Winthrop Aldrich.
- Herter, Christian A., Jr. & Mrs. Susan Cable Senior, 1955-1967 (Box 79, Folder 776)
  Correspondence re Mrs. Senior's activities and travels; letters of thanks for flowers; clippings; announcement of her marriage to Mr. Herter.
- Hickey, Margaret (Mrs. Joseph T. Strubinger), 1967 (Box 79, Folder 777)
  President of National Conference of Social Work. Letter re husband's illness. "We must pay for our own room on Earth" article. Lunch with NAR. Itinerary. Editorial on technical assistance. "New Diplomacy in India."
- Hill, Milt Dean, 1945-1961 (Box 79, Folder 778)
  Correspondence re Latin America and Mr. Hill's activities.
- Hilleboe, Herman E., Dr., 1961-1970 (Box 80, Folder 779)
  Correspondence to, from, and about Dr. Hilleboe for whom NAR wrote some letters of introduction in Los Angeles.
- Hines, Lewis G. - "Speeches PT 4", 1951 (Box 80, Folder 780)
  National Intercollegiate Christian Council; NAR invited to speak. Hines does instead. Clippings. Correspondents include Mrs. Edward Collier.
- Hisle, John Wayne, 1948-1971 (Box 80, Folder 781)
  Officer with Inter-American Affairs. Correspondence re Latin America, business concerns, International Basic Economy Corporation. Was on NAR's staff beginning 1946.
- Historical Societies - General, 1967-1968 (Box 80, Folder 782)
- Historical Societies - Historical Society of Rockland County, 1967 (Box 80, Folder 783)
  NAR a life member as of 1967. Contribution 1967.
- Historical Societies - Historical Society of the Tarrytowns, Inc., 1955-1971 (Box 80, Folder 784)
  NAR a member. Most material previous to 1960 destroyed. Notices of meetings; appeal for aid 1956 declined; request for NAR's papers declined.
- Hitchcock, Ethan Allen & Mrs. Elizabeth, 1958-1976 (Box 80, Folder 785)
  Correspondence with Mrs. Hitchcock re employment and with Mr. Hitchcock re Channel 13 Program. Memorial service for Elizabeth French Hitchcock.
- Hodges, Wetmore, 1938 (Box 80, Folder 786)
  Memorandum on the "present situation." Correspondents include George Harrison.
- Holman, Eugene, 1937-1960 (Box 80, Folder 787)
  Mr. Holman, President of Standard Oil. Letters re NAR's illness in Texas in 1937; invitations to speak; correspondence concerning Mr. Holman's activities; articles, speeches, gifts and vacations.
- Homes - General, 1958-1971 (Box 80, Folder 788)
  Appeals and invitations to speak declined. Requests are from children's and elderly people's homes.
- Homes - Victoria Home for Aged British Men & Women, Inc., 1968-1970 (Box 80, Folder 789)
  NAR served as Honorary Chairman of Committee in 1968. Contribution 1968. Progress and financial reports.
- Hoof and Mouth Disease, 1947-1950 (Box 80, Folder 790)
  Information on Vaccines, House Committee on Agriculture. Bill for research in United States. Articles, clippings. Correspondents include Robert J. Kleberg, Jr., Merrill Abbey.
- Hook, Charles R. Jr., 1954-1956 (Box 80, Folder 791)
  Interview as Deputy Postmaster General. Recommendations. Resigns to join Kudner Agency. Correspondents include Robert C. Fulton, Jr.
- Hoover, Herbert, 1963-1964 (Box 80, Folder 792)
  Congratulations on his gold medal. Proclamation by NAR on his death.
- Hoover, J. Edgar, 1943-1945 (Box 80, Folder 793)
  Mexico City Conference. NAR's thanks for help and information. Correspondents include Alex Hanebuth, Robert Wall, James Wright.
- Hopkins, Dr. Ernest M., died 8/13/64, 1941-1964 (Box 80, Folder 794)
  Would like NAR to come to Boston for Alumni Dinner. Cottie, Ann. Clippings of Editorials on his death. NAR letter to Ann.
  See also Dartmouth File.
- Horwitz, Leonard J., 1949-1950 (Box 80, Folder 795)
  Would like to see NAR for his thesis on the Braden-Peron Struggle in Argentina, 1949. Interview and supplementary material. Correspondents include Martha Dalrymple.
- Hospitals - General - Alabama through Louisiana, 1958-1971 (Box 80, Folder 796)
  Previous to 1958 destroyed. Appeals generally declined. NAR contributions to Norwalk Hospital, Connecticut, 1964; Hospital of Good Samaritan Medical Center, California, 1965; Eisenhower Medical Center, California, 1970.
- Hospitals - Alabama through Louisiana - Arizona, Southwestern Clinic & Research Institute, Inc., 1961-1967 (Box 81, Folder 797)
  NAR contribution 1961. Progress and Annual Reports.
- Hospitals - Alabama through Louisiana - Colorado, National Jewish Hospital at Denver, 1948-1966 (Box 81, Folder 798)
  Invitations and appeals declined. Some previous to 1958 destroyed.
- Hospitals - General - Maine through Wisconsin, 1958-1971 (Box 81, Folder 799)
  NAR contribution to Berkeley County Hospital 1951. Other appeals declined.
- Hospitals - Maine through Wisconsin - New Hampshire, Mary Hitchcock Memorial Hospital, 1936-1971 (Box 81, Folder 800)
  Appeals and invitations, most declined. NAR contributions in 1936, 1937, 1948, 1965. Form appeals destroyed. NAR, Chairman of Expansion Fund in 1965.
- Hospitals - Maine through Wisconsin - New York State - General, 1958-1971 (Box 81, Folder 801)
  Appeals declined. Prior to 1958 destroyed.
- Hospitals - Maine through Wisconsin - New York State - New Rochelle Hospital, 1951 (Box 81, Folder 802)
  NAR contribution 1951.
- Hospitals - Maine through Wisconsin - New York State - Phelps Memorial Hospital Association, Tarrytown (Formerly Tarrytown Hospital Association), 1932-1971 (Box 81, Folder 803)
  Appeals and invitations. 1932 appeal to join Board of Directors declined. NAR contributions 1951-1954, 1956. Rockefeller Brothers Fund contribution 1970.
- Hospitals - Maine through Wisconsin - New York State - White Plains Hospital, 1947-1960 (Box 81, Folder 804)
  Printed material destroyed. Correspondence re speaking engagement by NAR 1947. Appeals declined.
- Hospitals - Maine through Wisconsin - New York State - Long Island, Great Neck North Shore Hospital, Inc., 1951-1953 (Box 81, Folder 805)
- Hospitals - Maine through Wisconsin - New York State - New York City - General, 1952-1971 (Box 81, Folder 806)
  Appeals and invitations declined. Some previous to 1958 destroyed.
- Hospitals - Maine through Wisconsin - New York State - New York City - New York University (NYU) Medical Center, Institute of Physical Medicine and Rehabilitation, 1949-1971 (Box 81, Folder 807)
  Some appeals declined. NAR contribution 1961; Rockefeller Brothers Fund contribution 1968; Annual Reports.
- Hospitals - Maine through Wisconsin - New York State - New York City - Beth Israel Hospital, 1958 (Box 82, Folder 808)
  Appeal declined. Letter re laying of a cornerstone in 1958.
- Hospitals - Maine through Wisconsin - New York State - New York City - Knickerbocker Hospital, 1970-1971 (Box 82, Folder 809)
  NAR contribution 1971.
- Hospitals - Maine through Wisconsin - New York State - New York City - Memorial Hospital for Cancer & Allied Diseases and Memorial Sloan-Kettering Cancer Center, 1949-1971 (Box 82, Folder 810)
  Printed material; NAR contribution. Correspondents include Mrs. Laurance Spelman Rockefeller.
- Hospitals - Maine through Wisconsin - New York State - New York City - Mt. Morris Park Hospital, 1958-1962 (Box 82, Folder 811)
  NAR contributions 1958 & 1962.
- Hospitals - Maine through Wisconsin - New York State - New York City - New York Foundling Hospital, 1947-1960 (Box 82, Folder 812)
  NAR contributions 1947, 1951, 1959, 1960.
- Hospitals - Maine through Wisconsin - New York State - New York City - New York Infirmary, 1947-1970 (Box 82, Folder 813)
  NAR contribution to building fund 1949. Other appeals declined.
- Hospitals - Maine through Wisconsin - New York State - New York City - Roosevelt Hospital, 1949-1962 (Box 82, Folder 814)
  John Davison Rockefeller, Jr. and Rockefeller Center Incorporated contribution, 1957. No NAR contribution.
- Hospitals - Maine through Wisconsin - New York State - New York City - Society of New York Hospital - General, 1940-1961 (Box 82, Folder 815)
  Annual Reports; invitations declined; appeals for special projects declined.
- Hospitals - Maine through Wisconsin - New York State - New York City - Society of New York Hospital - Contributions, 1939-1967 (Box 82, Folder 816)
  NAR contributions, 1939, 1941-1942, 1946-1959, 1967.
- Hospitals - Maine through Wisconsin - New York State - New York City - Sydenham Hospital, 1947-1949 (Box 82, Folder 817)
  Appeals and invitations; ignored.
- Hospitals - Maine through Wisconsin - New York State - New York City - United Hospital Fund, 1948-1949 (Box 82, Folder 818)
  NAR arranged use of space in RCA building for benefit show, 1949.
- Hospitals - Maine through Wisconsin - New York State - New York City - United Hospital Fund - NAR Contributions & Correspondence, 1935-1941 (Box 82, Folder 819)
  NAR contributions, 1936-1940. Invitations declined.
- Hospitals - Foreign, 1951-1969 (Box 82, Folder 820)
  Majority of material previous to 1958 destroyed. Appeals declined.
- Housing - General (A-L), 1939-1971 (Box 83, Folder 821)
  Most material dated previous to 1959 discarded. Appeals for aid for or investment in housing projects. Proposals, clippings, material on Mutual Ownership Trust.
- Housing - General (M-Z), 1939-1971 (Box 83, Folder 822)
- Housing - New York State, 1959-1965 (Box 83, Folder 823)
  Projects; proposals.
- Housing - New York State - Citizens Housing & Planning Council of New York, Inc., 1937-1960 (Box 83, Folder 824)
  Publicity pamphlet. Invitations to NAR. Varied contributions, reports. Correspondents include Harold Buttenheim, Lawrence Orton, Yorke Allen.
- Housing - New York State - Citizens Housing & Planning Council of New York, Inc. - Printed Material, 1960-1969 (Box 83, Folder 825)
  Annual reports. Printed material for distribution. Bulletins.
- Housing - New York State - Citizens Housing & Planning Council of New York, Inc. - Contributions, 1941-1971 (Box 83, Folder 826)
  NAR contributions 1941-1945, 1947-1965, 1967-1971.
- Housing - Cooperative Homes of West Haven, Inc., 1948 (Box 84, Folder 827)
  Correspondence with Chester Bowles re this Company in Connecticut. Appeal to NAR for aid and advice from Mr. G. C. Gault.
- Housing - Projects - David Rockefeller, 1948-1951 (Box 84, Folder 828)
  Correspondence and memos re David Rockefeller's desire to support organizaed housing projects and legislation. NAR becomes interested in Morningside Heights and Manhattanville redevelopment and Mayor's Committee on Slum Clearance. Correspondents include David Rockefeller.
- Howard, Roy W., 1947-1951 (Box 84, Folder 829)
  Eugene Lyons' proposal concerning International Commission to Combat Slavery in Russia. NAR avoids committment. Museum of Modern Art. Invitations. "New York Sun-World Telegram" merger. Correspondents include Mr. Bartholomew.
- Hughes, Emmet John & Mrs. Katherine, 1956-1970 (Box 84, Folder 830)
  Correspondence re renting an apartment. Invitation to dinner. Letter re desk.
- Hughes, Richard J., Governor & Mrs., 1962-1964 (Box 84, Folder 831)
  Governor of New Jersey. Correspondence re Governors' Conference in 1963; invitation declined; congratulations on election.
- Human Rights, 1948-1959 (Box 84, Folder 832)
  Memos and letters re Human Rights Meetings. Progress of human rights groups. Appeals declined.
- Humphrey, Hubert, 1965, 1977 (Box 84, Folder 833)
  United States Vice President. Correspondence re NAR meeting with President Johnson in February 1965; letter of gratitude for NAR friendship, November 1977 (6 weeks before Humphrey died from cancer).
- Humphrey, Hubert, 1965, 1977 (Box 84, Folder 0833A)
  United States Vice President. Correspondence re NAR meeting with President Johnson in February 1965; letter of gratitude for friendship, November 1977 (6 weeks before Humphrey died of cancer).
- Hundred Year Association, 1954-1958 (Box 84, Folder 834)
  Annual Dinner Invitations. NAR congratulations to Sulzberger, to Sam Leidersdorf for Gold Medal Awards, 1958.
- I Miscellaneous, 1948-1971 (Box 84, Folder 835)
  Invitations and appeals declined. Correspondence re projects. Asking for advice. Some previous to 1960 discarded.
- Ibarra, M., 1955-1958 (Box 84, Folder 836)
  Praises NAR's Latin American work. Would like to have financial assistance for new book. Sends kind comments about NAR. Clippings.
- Ideas, Inventions, Patents, 1959-1970 (Box 84, Folder 837)
  Previous to 1959 discarded. Letters requesting aid in development of inventions or in obtaining patents.
- Immigration - General Correspondence, 1947-1955 (Box 84, Folder 838)
  Memos on immigration and refugee projects. Appeals declined. Clippings.
- India League of America, 1949-1953 (Box 84, Folder 839)
  NAR cannot advise re location for statue of Gandhi. Digest of Singh Statement. Dinner for Ambassador Mehta. Lunch for George Allen. Other invitations.
- Industrial Relations, 1949 (Box 84, Folder 840)
  Memos and letters re 1950 Industrial Public Relations Pattern Program for Roanoke, Virginia.
- Industrial Relations - Industrial Relations Counselors, Inc., 1949-1953 (Box 84, Folder 841)
  Reports on activities.
- Information Requests - General (A-G), 1965-1971 (Box 85, Folder 842)
  Previous to 1965 discarded. Requests for information on NAR, his interests and activities; also for information on miscellaneous subjects.
- Information Requests - General (H-M), 1965-1971 (Box 85, Folder 843)
- Information Requests - General (N-Z), 1965-1971 (Box 85, Folder 844)
- Information Requests - Maxwell, Allen B., Coordinator of Inter-American Affairs (Doctoral Thesis), 1967-1968 (Box 85, Folder 845)
  Correspondence re Maxwell's Ph.D. dissertation and material on NAR written for the 1968 campaign.
- Inman, Dr. Samuel Guy, 1949-1958 (Box 85, Folder 846)